Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Don't go forward.
لا تتقدم للأمام.
It's not safe ahead.
إنه ليس آمنًا في المستقبل.
Haven't you been here before?
ألم تكن هنا من قبل؟
Don't go forward.
لا تتقدم للأمام.
It's not safe ahead.
إنه ليس آمنًا في المستقبل.
Auntie.
عمة.
What did you just say?
ماذا قلت للتو؟
Don't go forward.
لا تتقدم للأمام.
It's not safe ahead.
إنه ليس آمنًا في المستقبل.
This place again.
هذا المكان مرة أخرى.
Don't go forward.
لا تتقدم للأمام.
It's not safe ahead.
إنه ليس آمنًا في المستقبل.
Who... who are you?
من...من أنت؟
I am you.
انا انت.
Have fun.
استمتع.
Soon I'll replace you.
سأحل محلك قريبا.
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
Master.
يتقن.
Is anyone there?
هل هناك أحد؟
Why is Grandpa taking so long this time?
لماذا يأخذ الجد وقتا طويلا هذه المرة؟
Old Ge, has Grandpa returned?
هل عاد الجد يا عزيزي؟
Miss.
يفتقد.
Bai Ye returned last night.
عاد باي يي الليلة الماضية.
But he's been staying in his room.
ولكنه بقي في غرفته.
Says he caught a chill.
يقول أنه أصيب بقشعريرة.
Miss.
يفتقد.
Bai Ye doesn't want to see anyone.
باي يي لا يريد رؤية أي شخص.
Says he'll be fine after sleeping.
يقول أنه سيكون بخير بعد النوم.
Did Bai Ye say anything else?
هل قال باي يي شيئا آخر؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Go about your business, Old Ge.
اذهب إلى عملك، أيها العجوز.
Bai Ye, it's me.
باي يي، أنا.
I heard you're ill.
سمعت أنك مريض.
Xiaowei made your favorite porridge.
شياووي صنع عصيدتك المفضلة.
Would you like some while it's hot?
هل ترغب في تناول بعضًا منها بينما هو ساخن؟
No need.
لا حاجة.
My chill is quite severe.
البرد عندي شديد جدًا.
Don't want to infect you.
لا أريد أن أصابك بالعدوى.
Not eating won't help.
عدم الأكل لن يساعد.
How about this.
ماذا عن هذا؟
I'll leave it by the door.
سأتركه عند الباب.
Remember to take it later.
تذكر أن تأخذها لاحقًا.
Laifu.
جريمة.
You.
أنت.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
I'm going to get medicine for Grandpa.
سأذهب لأحضر الدواء للجد.
Come with me.
تعال معي.
Grandpa can't stay like this.
لا يستطيع الجد أن يبقى هكذا.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Bai Ye.
باي يي.
I left dinner by your door.
لقد تركت العشاء عند بابك.
Xiaowei got you special
شياووي حصلت عليك خاصه
medicine for chills.
دواء للقشعريرة.
Remember to take it.
تذكر أن تأخذها.
Bai Ye.
باي يي.
Are you feeling better?
هل تشعر بتحسن؟
A bit better.
أفضل قليلا.
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
To cleanse myself.
لتطهير نفسي.
You must be feverish.
لابد أنك مصاب بالحمى.
The toilet's over there.
المرحاض هناك.
Perhaps
ربما
I'll take you.
سوف آخذك.
No need, young master.
لا داعي لذلك يا سيدي الشاب.
You dared to drug Grandpa?
هل تجرأت على إعطاء جدك مخدرًا؟
Aren't you afraid he'll punish you?
ألا تخاف من معاقبتك؟
Let me finish!
دعني أنهي!
I put laxative in his food,
أضع له ملينًا في طعامه،
but antidote in his medicine.
بل ترياق في دوائه.
He went at midnight,
ذهب في منتصف الليل،
so he ate but didn't take medicine.
فأكل ولم يتناول الدواء.
Meaning?
معنى؟
He's faking illness.
إنه يتظاهر بالمرض.
Grandpa's too old
الجد كبير في السن
to fake illness. Why?
التظاهر بالمرض. لماذا؟
To hide something.
إخفاء شيء ما.
And he seems unfamiliar here.
ويبدو أنه غير مألوف هنا.
Meaning?
معنى؟
I watched Bai Ye carefully.
لقد شاهدت باي يي بعناية.
I noticed he
لقد لاحظت أنه
eats and carries lanterns
يأكل ويحمل الفوانيس
with his right hand.
بيده اليمنى.
Grandpa's left-handed.
الجد أعسر.
So he's hiding
لذلك فهو يختبئ
to avoid contact with us.
لتجنب الاتصال بنا.
To not get exposed.
لكي لا تتعرض للخطر.
You mean
هل تقصد
my grandpa
جدي
isn't my grandpa?
أليس جدي؟
We need to investigate.
نحن بحاجة للتحقيق.
How?
كيف؟
Did Bai Ye say where he went?
هل قال باي يي إلى أين ذهب؟
Grandpa mentioned
ذكر الجد
he was investigating a case.
كان يحقق في قضية.
Checked the database.
تم التحقق من قاعدة البيانات.
There's a case related to what you mentioned.
هناك قضية تتعلق بما ذكرته.
One month ago,
منذ شهر واحد،
a girl named Hui Xin filed a report.
قدمت فتاة تدعى هوي شين بلاغًا.
She said her boyfriend Zhang Hua
قالت أن صديقها تشانغ هوا
was completely different after his business trip.
لقد كان مختلفًا تمامًا بعد رحلة عمله.
She even claimed
حتى أنها ادعت
the original Zhang Hua had died.
لقد مات تشانغ هوا الأصلي.
All information about this case
كافة المعلومات عن هذه القضية
is here.
هو هنا.
When we investigated,
عندما قمنا بالتحقيق،
some said Zhang Hua might've been possessed by an Ashen Shade.
قال البعض أن تشانغ هوا ربما كان مسكونًا بظل أشين.
But I think
ولكنني أعتقد
that's complete nonsense.
هذا هراء كامل.
Did she mention
هل ذكرت؟
how Zhang Hua was different?
كيف كان تشانغ هوا مختلفًا؟
Changed preferences,
تم تغيير التفضيلات،
altered memories,
ذكريات متغيرة،
and completely different daily routines.
والروتين اليومي مختلف تماما.
Exactly like Bai Ye's condition.
تمامًا مثل حالة باي يي.
You leave first.
أنت تغادر أولاً.
I need to talk with Laifu.
أريد أن أتحدث مع لايفو.
That's my grandfather!
هذا جدي!
Why can't I listen?
لماذا لا أستطيع الإستماع؟
It doesn't concern you.
لا يهمك .
Fine, I'm leaving.
حسنًا، سأغادر.
Speak.
يتكلم.
What do you want to say?
ماذا تريد أن تقول؟
Previously,
سابقًا،
that Tu Teng you asked me to investigate...
هذا تو تنغ الذي طلبت مني التحقيق فيه...
I have findings.
لقد وجدت نتائج.
But the deeper I looked,
ولكن كلما نظرت بعمق،
the more I realized at my level,
كلما أدركت ذلك في مستواي،
the information I can access is very limited.
المعلومات التي أستطيع الوصول إليها محدودة للغاية.
What you're planning to do
ما تخطط للقيام به
could be very dangerous.
قد يكون خطيرًا جدًا.
As a friend,
كصديق،
I advise against it.
أنصح بعدم فعل ذلك.
I could hire you as a special consultant.
أستطيع أن أقوم بتعيينك كمستشار خاص.
You'd be set for life.
سوف تكون مستعدًا مدى الحياة.
Why must you
لماذا يجب عليك
insist on involving yourself
أصر على إشراك نفسك
in something potentially fatal?
في شيء قد يكون قاتلا؟
Officer Gu,
الضابط جو
everyone has their own destiny.
كل شخص لديه مصيره الخاص.
I have mine.
انا عندي.
Bai Ye showed me kindness.
لقد أظهر لي باي يي اللطف.
These Tu Teng
هذه تو تنغ
are connected to my family's death.
مرتبطة بوفاة عائلتي.
There's blood debt here.
هناك دين الدم هنا.
Be it man, ghost or spirit,
سواء كان رجلاً أو شبحًا أو روحًا،
debts will be repaid,
سيتم سداد الديون،
wrongs will be righted.
سيتم تصحيح الأخطاء.
What exactly is the truth?
ما هي الحقيقة بالضبط؟